# https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&category=15&difficulty=easy&type=boolean
question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In Until Dawn, both characters Sam and Mike cannot be killed under any means until the final chapter of the game.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The protagonist of Dead Rising 3 is called Chuck Greene.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the Monster Hunter Series, it is possible to capture Elder Dragons.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the Mortal Kombat series the &quot;Deadly Alliance&quot; consists of Shang Tsung and Quan Chi",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  ]

